Suddenly, are you all close?
Yes, we are.
Do you have any good stories?
I play with Saayan and Grandyan, sometimes.
We are in the same unit.
We have the same unit, Journey Go Trip.
We often do live shows together.
We spend a lot of time together.
When I first started YouTube a year ago
It was a real mystery.
That's for sure.
But through this YouTube
We started doing projects together, two or three at a time, and we gradually got to know each other.
We gradually got to know each other.
It's definitely reassuring.
The reason I asked this question is because
It's not often that all five of us get together for a YouTube project.
You know, and all five of us together.
The reason given by the office was that our schedules don't match.
I wonder if that's really the case.
Actually, I'm not sure.
Maybe the five of us don't get along.
No, no, no, no, no.
That's not true.
So if someone's in danger.
You mean, if one of us is in danger, the rest of us will go to his rescue?
That's what I suspect.
I'd like you to show us how it's done.
Oh.
That's what we're trying to do this time.
Oh!
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
I'm so excited!
Yes, as for the contents...
We have five games for you to try.
Yes, sir.
Each game will be played with one hostage.
Hostage? Hostage?
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Five hundred.
And the four of you who remain...
You're going to help us rescue those hostages.
Heh.
Oh, man.
By the way, what is the goal of ST4DF this year?
Seino
Go above and beyond!
Yes, of course!
This is the challenge that you are going to take on.
The four of you will take on the challenge one at a time.
If all four of you complete the challenge, you will be rescued.
But you have to bark at the person in front of you.
That's what we're going to do this time.
By the way, if you can't rescue the hostage
a balloon will be placed in front of the hostage
and it will be broken in front of your eyes.
Ehhhh...
Oh, no.
Of course you can rescue them all?
Let's do it.
Let's do our best.
The first hostage will be Mr. Imamura.
I'm sorry, it's Mr. Imamura.
Is it dangerous to be a hostage?
It's so close.
To be rescued, the challenge is to catch soybeans! I see.
But I'm Japanese and use chopsticks on a regular basis.
I used them the day before, so I think I can do it.
How about you, Mr. Imamura?
We'll have four. - Right.
We need to make a decision here, and have it succeed, and have everyone get into a good flow here.
That's right.
Yes, please.
We'll decide the order together.
Well, then, come on!
What?
People who don't get old and are getting old.
Old people.
Older people.
The older ones have been using the bridge longer.The top one is still the one with the longest race using the bridge.
The first one is Lissen.
Ya!
Second is me.
Third is Mr. Relay.
Last is Saya.
Ten.
Ten?
Here we go.
I'll do my best.
Okay, first one.
Actually transfer 3 pieces within 30 seconds.
Here we go.
Ready, start!
Go for it!
Go, go, go, go, go! Go, go, go, go, go!
Go like this! Go like this!
Slowly! Slowly!
Keep going like this! Go like this!
Keep calm! Stay calm! Stay calm!
Nine seconds elapsed! Whoa! No! Go for him! Take him! Stay calm! Stay calm! You have nine seconds!
Whoa!
Oh, no! It worked!
Oh, thank God!
I was in a bit of a rush!
Even a little bit.
Yes, you were.
Surprisingly, I got three in 10 seconds.
Now five in 30 seconds!
Five this time in 30 seconds!
Good luck! Let's go!
Good luck! Go for it! Go for it!
Fast! Fast!
Fast!
Yes!
Yes! Yes! Clear!
That's great!
Fast!
Yes! I kept my composure.
It's okay if the number of yasus increases all at once.
Go for it! The third one is seven in 30 seconds!
Fast forward to the start!
One.
All right...
Stay cool.
It's okay.
Three.
Four.
It's okay.
Five.
You can do it.
Ten seconds elapsed.
Six.
One more to go.
Seven.
Congratulations, boo-boo.
I've got the most... boo-boos...
Oh, boo-boo, boo-boo, boo-boo, boo-boo.
What do you mean "tease"? Give me back my foot, please.
What?
Oh, my God!
Why, why, why, why?
Why, why, why, why? I didn't hear you.
The line's gripping.
Hey!
Don't make it easy sometimes.
Make it harder all the time.
I can do it! Come on! If it's easy, it's hard!
Keep trying!
Ten in 30 seconds.
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Come on, come on, come on! Slowly!
Calm down! Stay calm!
Come on, come on, come on! Oh, I'm ready! ...  What? Five, four, three, two, one.Go, go, go, go! Oh, I'm ready,! What? Five, four, three, two, one.
Whoa!
That was close!
Yeah!
That's great!
Scary!
Watch out!
Oh, my God!
Well done!
Yes!
Mr. Yamada, it's Kirs!
Good job! Good!
I'm so happy! Thank you!
What do you think? What do you think, Mr. Yamamura?
They were all great.
Especially, the change of ends, just 2 more seconds off,
Add the addition.
Mr. Yamamura was so cute! Yamamura-san was "kyun!".
He was absolutely smitten! Oh, my God!
Oh no! Oh no! Palette than the person in question. Boo-boo
Boo-boo none.
The next hostage is Shinasa!
Ohhhh why do I have to ask you to do a challenge to rescue me, like the assumption that I'm already going to ring
Trash Can Throwing Challenge
Throwing in the trash
Throw a piece of paper into a large trash can at the foot of Shizuoka-san.
Throw a piece of paper into the big trash can at Mr. Shizuoka's feet.
The first one is 1 person
The second one was 1.5
The third person is two, and the fourth and last person is 1.5 meters, the third person is 2 meters
And the fourth and last one is 3 meters.
Wow, that's a lot!
So many!
What's the first one like?
I'll go first.
Yes, please.
Yeah, go for it!
Okay, Mr. Takao, first one meter.
Please.
Please do.
Here we go.
What?
What? What? What?
Look! This!
We're all at one meter!
Fill it up. 2.5 meters, 1.5 meters, 1.5 meters.
Here we go.
Wow.
Well, this is...
Okay, then.
Second one, 1.5 meters.
Round one.
Here we go.
Okay, round two, round one.
Round two, please.
2.5 meters, please.
Good luck.
That was good.
That was a little close.
But you did it!
That was a little close. But, you know, it was good!
It's pretty easy to burn.
And the third one...
Imamura.
Second one.
Captain
I'll do my best!
Then, please!
Please, please, please!
Too bad, Mr. Imamura, why don't you cuse me.
But I'm here.
No, no, no, no.
If you do it alone, you'll end up doing it.
But I want you to do it once.
I want you to do it once, and I want you to do it right.
I want you to do about three meters of Rine.
I want you to do it.I want you to do it.
I'll be a little creative.
Higher density so it doesn't become a body.
Please, please, please, please. Don't be light, goofy. Higher density. I'll show you. Please please please.
Please, please, please.
Here we go.
Ready!
Woooo!
Yay!
Here it comes!
It's the best. I knew it! It's the best!
Yay!
Now, I have a special treat for you.
Mr. Imamura.
Three meters out.
Yes!
Yay!
But I overdid it earlier.
I was flying too fast, so I might be able to get in.
Just in time.
If this goes in, there's no penalty, right?
I'll do my best.
You asked for it, Mr. Uchi.
3 meters, please, Mr. Imamura.
Please.
Please, fast-forward.
Wow! Wow! and then, unfortunately, Mr. Shimono, you have become a recipient. Now, please.
Aaaaahhhh!
If you found this video interesting, please give it a high rating and subscribe to our channel!
Watch the next video too!
Please subscribe to our channel!
Watch the next video!